mingle about you know back in 2019 uh
Manulife was granted its operating
license here in Myanmar that was a very
proud moment for manual life because as
many of you know we were re-entering the
market here having been here back in
1902.
and so it was a very exciting time for
us and I would just like to take this
opportunity of thanking all of you we
have over 120 staff for the work and the
journey that you've been on in the last
three years it really has been a
fantastic journey and a great compliment
to you that you've been able to build
our business I'd also like to thank our
customers who have put their trust in
Manulife to help them ensure that they
have security for the future our product
is actually one of the best products you
can buy because it pays out the most
when you need it the most
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]